Hello, this video is an introduction of BillardGL.
BillardGL is a billiard game on PC-Unix.
Its graphics using OpenGL is beautiful.
I played it on FreeBSD 9.0/amd64.
The graphics card was ASUS GT440 with NVIDIA GeForce GT440 GPU.
Now I start explaining how to play this game.
I am at "View" mode.
I can swing the camera with dragging the left button of my mouse.
Dragging the right button horizontally moves the camera.
Vertical dragging of the right button zooms in/out.
I can aiso zoom in/out with Page Up/Down of a keyboard.
Insert/Delete buttons changes vertical position of the camera.
Function keys from F1 to F8 change view.
Cursor keys on the keyboard moves the camera's position.
I can focus a ball by clicking one of balls at bottom of the screen.
When you push a space bar, you will be in "Aim" mode.
In Aim mode, view rotates around the white ball.
When you decide direction, press the space bar. Don't release immediately.
You will shot on releasing the key.
You can replay the last shot with the "r" key.
You can replay as many times as you like.
At last, I explain "Place White" mode.
When you drop the white ball, mode will be changed to "Place White" mode.
In this mode, cursor keys can change position of the white ball.
To exit the game, please click the logo at top-left corner.
Notice
I changed the settings of controls before recording this video.
I inverted X/Y-axis. It is natural for me.
And one more notice.
You must find that some parts in the screen blink.
It was a broblem of recording.
They did not blink in the actual screen.
My explanation is over.
Danke. Enjoy!